newsblaster.com 2012-12-07

# Kanatsiz Communications, Inc. Privacy Statement

            Kanatsiz Communications, Inc. Privacy Statement
This document was last updated on January 2, 2010.
1. ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
Kanatsiz Communications, Inc. (“KCOMM”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This
Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information
we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing KCOMM
at www.kcomm.com or www.kanatsiz.com, you acknowledge and fully understand
KCOMM’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use
practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.
2. PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor or affiliated
sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the
corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who
participate in KCOMM services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy
initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since
we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants
and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of
those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies
of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or
complete any transaction with such parties.
3. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT
KCOMM collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from
our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.
     a. Web Server Logs.
     When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and
     analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:
        Your Internet protocol address.
        The kind of browser or computer you use.
        Number of links you click within the site.
        State or country from which you accessed the site.
        Date and time of your visit.
        Name of your Internet service provider.
        Web page you linked to our site from.
        Pages you viewed on the site.
                     KCOMM Privacy Statement – 2010 – All Rights Reserved                   1

     B. Use of Cookies
KCOMM may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is
a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot
be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely
assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the
cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you
time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie
helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this
simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by
providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing
personalized functionality..
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If
you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may
disable some of the functionality on our Website.
     c. Personal Information Users
Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will
request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or
facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing
a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is
used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this
information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of
registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose
personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For
example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and
troubleshooting.
We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third
parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:
        To fulfill your service requests for services.
        To protect ourselves from liability,
        To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
        In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.
4. USE OF WEB BEACONS OR GIF FILES
KCOMM web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons –
sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow KCOMM to count users who have
visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. KCOMM may include Web
beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether
messages have been opened and acted upon.
Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help
determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications.
These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent
                      KCOMM Privacy Statement – 2010 – All Rights Reserved                2

cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer
each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in
relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn
which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site.
KCOMM prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal
information.
5. ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION
We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in
your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by
contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant – info@kcomm.com.
6. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
KCOMM has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do,
we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you
to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping
to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service
constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
7. CONTACTING US
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to
adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at
info@kcomm.com or send your comments to :
KCOMM
Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel
10 Mar del Rey
San Clemente, California 92673
KCOMM will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any
problem or question.
                    KCOMM Privacy Statement – 2010 – All Rights Reserved                 3
